

# FATMA KESKIN

Profile

I am self employed and working in education sector. I would like to change my career and work in IT. Have an interest and experience in website design. Strong creative and analytical skills.

Team player with an eye for detail. Native Turkish speaker. Advanced level English (IELTS 7.5)

# EXPERIENCE

#### **DIRECTOR**

Felicity Consultation Services Ltd.

## **2017 - Present**

- Project Manager at Mothership Projects
- Mentor
- Turkish Tutor

#### SECONDARY SCHOOL TEACHER

Religious Education Teacher

### 2012 - 2016

- Worked at schools in Turkiye and Australia
- Taught Year 4 up to Year 9
- Excelled in classroom management

#### **PROJECT MANAGER**

Turkish Finance Instution and NGOs

## 2004 - 2008

- Officer at Foreign Transactions Department
- Manager at University Students' Residential Hall
- Project Manager at Empowering Women Charity

**1** 07514-821-301

✓ akkesfatm@gmail.com



2 70 Abbey Crescent, Oldbury, B68 9HN. West Midlands



felicityeducation.co.uk

# EDUCATION

## **BACHELOR OF THEOLOGY**

Sakarya University

2008-2012

#### **BACHELOR OF ECONOMICS**

Bogazici University

2000 - 2004

# SKILLS

- Positive and Enthusiastic
- Team Leader
- Understanding and Respecting Cultural Values
- Strong Communication
- Computer Literacy and Web Design
- Project Management Tools
- Problem-Solving